Aleksander Brown

Software Developer

alekjbrown@live.com ≥

(515)771-5940

Des Moines, Iowa

linkedin.com/in/AleksanderBrown in

github.com/Alekjbrown

Student in Information Technology at Des Moines Area Community College. Diagnostic and technical experience as an Automotive Technician that encouraged skill growth in unique problem solving and a talent in finding technical information and quick resolutions. Experience in staff management, records keeping, database maintenance, and more.

TECHNICAL SKILLS



EDUCATION

AAS Computer Information

Des Moines Area Community College

Expected December 2020 Courses

- Java

- c#

- c# ASP.NET Core

- HTML/CSS

Ankenv.IA

- Data Structures

- SQL

- Business

AAS Automotive Technology

Des Moines Area Community College May 2012

PROJECT

Course Scheduler

Des Moines Senior College

01/2020 - present

- Design and code automated scheduling for course offerings
- github.com/Alekjbrown/SeniorCollegeScheduler

ORGANIZATIONS

Hackerrank

05/2018 - present

Codewars

01/2020 - present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Warehouse

Nott Company

07/2016 - 12/2019 Urbandale.IA Leading and respected supplier of fluid power products and systems.

- Managed staff of three or more employees
- Kept accurate records of receipts and shipping forms
- Designed and implemented MS Access database
- Managed Inventory
- On-time product fulfillment
- Evaluated and improved operating processes

Automotive Technician

Various companies

2006 - 2016

Des Moines.IA

- Designed and maintained database for customers, products, services, pricing, expenses, and more
- Diagnosed and repaired all vehicle systems including electronics and software
- Managed schedules for employees and tasks
- Managed and met tight deadlines for customers on a
- Installed facility technical solutions such as computers, networks, video security, vehicle lifts, and more
- Versed in technical information usage